Amy: Twelve thirty. In a long queue outside the Conference Centre in Manchester.
Guard: Can I see your ID, please?
Amy: Here’s my passport.
Guard: Thanks. ‘Amy Jones.’ And I need to check your bag, please.
OK, that’s fine, come in. Next, please!
Amy: Twelve forty-five. In the waiting area with three hundred and fifty other singers!
Organizer 1: OK Amy, sit here and wait until we call your name.
Amy: Thanks.
Organizer: Are you here for the audition, too?
Friend: No, I’m not. I’m Amy’s friend. Can I wait with her?
Organizer 1: Yeah, sure.
Friend: Thanks.
Amy: Let’s sit here. I’m so nervous…
Organizer 1: Matteo Ricci, Jada Jackson, Tony Cash, come with me, please. This way.
Amy: Good luck!
Four o’clock. Three hours later! My turn at last!
Organizer 2: Amy Jones, Naomi Williams, Dan Elliot? Can you come with me, please? It’s your turn now.
Amy: Oh help! It’s my turn.
Friend: Good luck, Amy! You can do it!
Amy: Excuse me. Can my friend come with me?
Organizer 2: No, she can’t. She can wait there.
And you can’t take your bag into the audition. Leave it with your friend.
Amy: OK.
Four fifteen. In the audition, with two judges. Really nervous!
Judge: Amy … Jones? What’s your song?
Amy: One Day.
Judge: We can’t hear you. Is the microphone on?
Amy: Sorry. Sorry. Can you hear me now?
Judge: Yes, that’s fine.
Amy: My song’s One Day.
Judge: Can you start, please?
Amy: Oh no! I can’t remember the first line.
Judge: Take your time.
Amy: I’m OK now!